Texas Governor George W. Bush:
Texas State Library and Archives Commission
- Governor George W. Bush General Counsel's settlement files, 1991-1996, bulk 1995-1996, 7 cubic ft.
  - Group one settlement files, January-October 1995
    - Grover, Charman vs. MHMR, 1995 (Box 2002/151-322)
    - Grubbs, Jonathan and Alex Herbert vs. MHMR, 1995 (Box 2002/151-322)
    - Grayum, C. Richard vs. Texas Board of Architectural Examiners, 1994-1995 (Box 2002/151-322)
    - Box 2 inventory (Box 2002/151-323)
    - Hackney, Howard and Joanna, State Farm Insurance Co. vs. Texas Historical Commission, 1995 (Box 2002/151-323)
    - Hamann, Allen and Matyasi, Beverly and Tim vs. MHMR, 1995 (Box 2002/151-323)
    - Harper, Clara vs. MHMR, 1995 (Box 2002/151-323)
    - Harrison, Nancy vs. MHMR, 1995 (Box 2002/151-323)
    - Hassell, R.L. vs, MHMR, 1995 (Box 2002/151-323)
    - Hedge, Chris vs. TDCJ, 1995 (Box 2002/151-323)
    - Helmcamp, Susan vs. MHMR, 1995 (Box 2002/151-323)
    - Herman vs. UT Medical Branch, 1995 (Box 2002/151-323)
    - Herman vs. UT Medical Branch, 1995 (Box 2002/151-323)
    - Hernandez, Albert, et al. vs. UT Medical Center, et al, 1995 (Box 2002/151-323)
    - Hodge, Warren Neal vs. Mexia State School, 1993-1995, [Contains possibly excepted information: common law privacy - name of resident in state school] (Box 2002/151-323)
    - Hoffman, Linda and Bob vs. Dr. Rinn - indemnification, 1995 (Box 2002/151-323)
    - Hohenberger vs. State of Texas and DPS, 1995 (Box 2002/151-323)
    - Holloway, Elease vs. MHMR, 1995, [Contains possibly excepted information: common law privacy - name of resident in state school] (Box 2002/151-323)
    - Holmes, Christina vs. DPS, 1995 (Box 2002/151-323)
    - Hoskins, Neccia vs. MHMR, 1995 (Box 2002/151-323)
    - Huff, Dallas vs. UT Medical Branch, 1995 (Box 2002/151-323)
    - Hurlbut, Brenda vs. MHMR, 1995 (Box 2002/151-323)
    - Inman, Jerry vs. TDCJ, 1995 (Box 2002/151-323)
    - Jarrett, Carla vs. TDCJ, 1995 (Box 2002/151-323)
    - Johnson, Betty vs. Pan American University, 1994-1995, [Contains possibly excepted information: common law privacy] (Box 2002/151-323)
    - Johnson, Bryan vs. MHMR, 1995 (Box 2002/151-323)
    - Johnson, Carl and Sheila, Allstate Insurance Co. vs. TDCJ, 1995 (Box 2002/151-323)
    - Johnson, Eunice D. vs. TPWD, 1995 (Box 2002/151-323)
    - Johnson, Shirley vs. TDCJ, 1995 (Box 2002/151-323)
    - Jones, Marty and Michelle vs. Robert Saffell and TDCJ, 1994-1995 (Box 2002/151-323)
    - Joseph, Jimmy vs. MHMR, 1995 (Box 2002/151-323)
    - Keisler, Gary Neil, et al. vs. TDCJ, 1994-1995 (Box 2002/151-323)
    - Kendrick, Leanne vs. East Texas State University, 1995 (Box 2002/151-323)
    - Kenney, Bobby vs. MHMR, 1995 (Box 2002/151-323)
    - Khalaf, Wajeh vs. MHMR, 1995 (Box 2002/151-323)
    - Klepper, Douglas, MD, indemnification, 1995 (Box 2002/151-323)
    - Kunkel, Cornell vs. MHMR, 1995 (Box 2002/151-323)
    - Lambremont, Connie and Mary John vs. TPWD, 1995 (Box 2002/151-323)
    - Law, Melissa and William vs. TPWD, 1995 (Box 2002/151-323)
    - Lawler, Daniel vs. MHMR, 1995 (Box 2002/151-323)
    - Lawson, Grant vs. Texas A I University, 1995, [Contains possibly excepted information: common law privacy] (Box 2002/151-323)
    - Lawson, James vs. Region IV Education Service Center and Texas Education Agency, 1995 (Box 2002/151-323)
    - Leonard, Ted vs. Texas School for the Deaf, 1995, [Contains possibly excepted information: common law privacy - name of student in state school] (Box 2002/151-323)
    - Leslz, et al. vs. Kavanagh, MD, et al, 1995 (Box 2002/151-323)
    - Lewis, Charlia vs. Texas Rehabilitation Commission, 1995, [Contains possibly excepted information: common law privacy] (Box 2002/151-323)
    - Lexington Hotel Suites vs. DPS, 1995 (Box 2002/151-323)
    - Liddell, Marie vs. MHMR, 1995 (Box 2002/151-323)
    - Lira, Felipe vs. TYC, 1995 (Box 2002/151-323)
    - Little, Doyle Randy vs. MHMR, 1995 (Box 2002/151-323)
    - Little, Faye vs. Texas Department of Agriculture, 1995 (Box 2002/151-323)
    - Lopez, Adrian vs. Texas Attorney General's Office, 1995 (Box 2002/151-323)
    - Lozano, Leonard vs. Jeanne Fox, et al. (Texas Alcoholic Beverage Commission (TABC)), 1992-1995 (Box 2002/151-323)
    - Lozano, Leonard J. vs. Jeanne Fox, et al. (TABC), 1995 (Box 2002/151-323)
    - Lyon, Kaylynne vs. TDPRS, 1995, [Contains possibly excepted information: common law privacy] (Box 2002/151-323)
    - McCollough, W. Scott vs. Dan Morales, 1995 (Box 2002/151-323)
    - McCracken, H.L. Company vs. TDCJ, 1995 (Box 2002/151-323)
    - McKinney, Luana vs. State of Texas, 1995 (Box 2002/151-323)
    - McKinney, Garland L. vs. MHMR, 1995 (Box 2002/151-323)
    - McNabb, Tamara and Allstate Insurance Co. vs. TDCJ, 1995 (Box 2002/151-323)
    - Magnuson, William vs. TDCJ, 1995 (Box 2002/151-323)
    - Majeski, Karen vs. DPS, 1995 (Box 2002/151-323)
    - Majeski, Karen vs. DPS, 1995 (Box 2002/151-323)
    - Martin, Donald W., Jr. vs. DHS, 1995 (Box 2002/151-323)
    - Martin, J. vs. DPS, 1995 (Box 2002/151-323)
    - Martin, Tabatha vs. Texas Department of Health, 1995 (Box 2002/151-323)
    - Mason, Sam and Pertina vs. TYC, 1995 (Box 2002/151-323)
    - Master, Ruiz Special vs. TDCJ, 1995 (Box 2002/151-323)
    - Meerman, Leo vs. MHMR, 1995 (Box 2002/151-323)
    - Mendez, M. vs. Texas Dept. of Health, 1995, [Contains possibly excepted information: common law privacy] (Box 2002/151-323)
    - Mentch, Bill vs. DPS, 1995 (Box 2002/151-323)
    - Mercer, Patrick vs. MHMR, 1995 (Box 2002/151-323)
    - Millian, Lori Ann vs. MHMR, 1995 (Box 2002/151-323)
    - Mittanck vs. MHMR, 1995 (Box 2002/151-323)
    - Moff, Ashton Rene vs. Attorney General, 1995, [Contains possibly excepted information: common law privacy] (Box 2002/151-323)
    - Molina, George, et al. vs. Texas Tech University Health Science Center, 1995 (Box 2002/151-323)
    - Moorehead, Jamie vs. MHMR, 1995 (Box 2002/151-323)
    - Morrow, Albert vs. DPS, 1995 (Box 2002/151-323)
    - Munoz, Steve vs. Comptroller, 1995 (Box 2002/151-323)
    - Murillo, Berne vs. Texas A M University, 1995 (Box 2002/151-323)
    - Nam, Hyan Kyung Jane vs. DPS, 1995 (Box 2002/151-323)
    - Nemons, Greg vs. MHMR, 1995 (Box 2002/151-323)
    - Nichols, D. vs. Texas Dept. of Health, 1995, [Contains possibly excepted information: home address of state employee, common law privacy] (Box 2002/151-323)
    - Oklahoma Turnpike Authority vs. GSC, 1995 (Box 2002/151-323)
    - Osmond, James and David Krisch vs. TDCJ, 1995 (Box 2002/151-323)
    - Osmond, James and David Krisch vs. TDCJ, 1995 (Box 2002/151-323)
    - Owens, Alethea vs. TPWD, 1995 (Box 2002/151-323)
    - Padget, Marie vs. UT Medical Branch, 1995 (Box 2002/151-323)
    - Parish, Michael E. vs. TABC, 1995 (Box 2002/151-323)
    - Parsons, Travis vs. UT Health Center, 1995 (Box 2002/151-323)
    - Pearson, W.L. vs. DHS, 1995 (Box 2002/151-323)
    - Penn, Sylvia vs. Comptroller, 1995, [Contains possibly excepted information: common law privacy] (Box 2002/151-323)
    - Perez, Sergio vs. MHMR, 1995 (Box 2002/151-323)
    - Perry, Percie vs. MHMR, 1995 (Box 2002/151-323)
    - Polilowsk, Dale vs. MHMR, 1995 (Box 2002/151-323)
    - Polston, Ronnie vs. MHMR, 1995 (Box 2002/151-323)
    - Ponzio, Denise vs. Texas A M University System, 1995 (Box 2002/151-323)
    - Presley, Melinda and Jeffrey vs. MHMR, 1995 (Box 2002/151-323)
    - Pope, Glenda Sue vs. Southwest Texas State University, 1995 (Box 2002/151-323)
    - Powell, Richard and Phyllis vs. Texas A M University, 1995 (Box 2002/151-323)
    - Presley, Marti vs. TDCJ, 1995 (Box 2002/151-323)
    - Quiroga, Gabriel vs. TABC, 1995 (Box 2002/151-323)
    - Box 3 inventory (Box 2002/151-323)
    - R.A.J., et al. vs. Dennis Jones and MHMR, 1995 (Box 2002/151-323)
    - R.A.J., et al. vs. Don Gilbert, 1995 (Box 2002/151-323)
    - R.A.J., et al. vs. MHMR, 1995 (Box 2002/151-323)
    - Ramirez, Irma vs. El Paso Hospital District, 1994-1995 (Box 2002/151-323)
    - Rangel, Debra vs. MHMR, 1995 (Box 2002/151-323)
    - Rastegar vs. Texas Dept. of Health, 1995 (Box 2002/151-324)
    - Raumaker, Wendy vs. DPS, 1995, [Contains possibly excepted information: common law privacy] (Box 2002/151-324)
    - Reed, Troy vs. TDCJ, 1995 (Box 2002/151-324)
    - Reyna, Guillermina and Hector vs. Glenn Fluellen, et al, vs. DPS, 1995, [Contains possibly excepted information: common law privacy] (Box 2002/151-324)
    - Roberdeau, Eugenia vs. TDPRS, 1995, [Contains possibly excepted information: common law privacy] (Box 2002/151-324)
    - Robinowitz vs. Texas State Board of Dental Examiners, 1994-1995 (Box 2002/151-324)
    - Rocha, Antonio, Jr. vs. Comptroller, 1994-1995, [Contains possibly excepted information: common law privacy] (Box 2002/151-324)
    - Rodriguez, Jose vs. Yda Aleman and Rio Grande State Center (MHMR), 1994-1995 (Box 2002/151-324)
    - Rodriguez, Ruby and Amado vs. DPS, 1995 (Box 2002/151-324)
    - Rodriguez, Melinda vs. MHMR, 1995 (Box 2002/151-324)
    - Romero, Manuelita vs. MHMR, 1995 (Box 2002/151-324)
    - Round Rock Plumbing Co., Inc. vs. MHMR, 1995 (Box 2002/151-324)
    - Ruby, Jerry vs. TDCJ, 1995 (Box 2002/151-324)
    - Russell, David vs. DPS, 1995 (Box 2002/151-324)
    - Rutherford, Toni and Mike vs. MHMR. 1995 (Box 2002/151-324)
    - Sanchez, Elizandro vs. MHMR, 1995 (Box 2002/151-324)
    - Santacruz, Carmen and Steve vs. GLO, 1995 (Box 2002/151-324)
    - Schoppa, C.J. vs. TPWD, 1995 (Box 2002/151-324)
    - Scott, Patricia vs. MHMR, 1995 (Box 2002/151-324)
    - Shwarts, Kalman, J., MD - indemnification, 1995 (Box 2002/151-324)
    - Sierra Club vs. Bruce Babbitt, et al, 1995, [3 folders] (Box 2002/151-324)
    - Simmons, Helen vs. MHMR, 1995 (Box 2002/151-324)
    - Simmons, Mary vs. UT Health Science Center, 1995 (Box 2002/151-324)
    - Simpson, Jane vs. MHMR, 1995 (Box 2002/151-324)
    - Singleton, William, MD - indemnification, 1995 (Box 2002/151-324)
    - Smith, Francis G. and H. Lester, Jr., and Aetna Casualty and Surety Co. vs. MHMR, 1995 (Box 2002/151-324)
    - Smith, Pat vs. DHS, 1995 (Box 2002/151-324)
    - Smith, Richard vs. Attorney General's Office, 1995, [Contains possibly excepted information: common law privacy] (Box 2002/151-324)
    - Smith, Wesley, et al. vs. MHMR, 1995, [Contains possibly excepted information: common law privacy] (Box 2002/151-324)
    - Speer, Dana vs. MHMR, 1995 (Box 2002/151-324)
    - Stogner, Katrina vs. MHMR, 1995 (Box 2002/151-324)
    - Straughan, John vs. GSC, 1995 (Box 2002/151-324)
    - Swatloski, Paul and Francis V. vs. Texas Department of Transportation (TxDOT), 1995 (Box 2002/151-324)
    - Synek, Miroslav vs. UT San Antonio, 1995, [Contains possibly excepted information: common law privacy] (Box 2002/151-324)
    - Tadlock, Paul vs. MHMR, 1995 (Box 2002/151-324)
    - Tatum, Russell vs. TPWD, 1995 (Box 2002/151-324)
    - Tatum, Sam vs. DPS, 1995 (Box 2002/151-324)
    - Taylor, Windle vs. GSC, 1995 (Box 2002/151-324)
    - Tenant Tracker, Inc. vs. DPS, 1995 (Box 2002/151-324)
    - Teneco Properties, Inc. vs. MHMR, 1995 (Box 2002/151-324)
    - Tennant, Sonya vs. TDCJ, 1995 (Box 2002/151-324)
    - Terrazas, Louis, et al. vs. Bob Shagle, et al, 1995 (Box 2002/151-324)
    - Texas Center for Policy Studies vs. Dan Morales, 1995 (Box 2002/151-324)
    - Texas, State of vs. United States, 1995 (Box 2002/151-324)
    - Tickles, R.F. vs. TDCJ, 1995 (Box 2002/151-324)
    - Tijmes, Jorge E. - indemnification, 1995 (Box 2002/151-324)
    - Tilbury, Dolores vs. TPWD, 1995, [Contains possibly excepted information: home address of state employee] (Box 2002/151-324)
    - Townsend, Shelly vs. MHMR, 1995 (Box 2002/151-324)
    - Triplett, G. vs. UT Health Science Center, 1995, [Contains possibly excepted information: common law privacy] (Box 2002/151-324)
    - Trlicek, Debra Ann vs. MHMR, 1995 (Box 2002/151-324)
    - Trolinger, Rolland and State Farm Mutual Auto Insurance vs. Texas Dept. of Health, 1995 (Box 2002/151-324)
    - TU Electric vs. DPS, 1995 (Box 2002/151-324)
    - Ulrich, JoAnn vs. MHMR, 1995 (Box 2002/151-324)
    - Underwood, Barbara Maria vs. State of Texas, et al, 1995 (Box 2002/151-324)
    - United States vs. Texas Dept. of Agriculture, 1995 (Box 2002/151-324)
    - Vain, Carol Ann Manuel vs. DPS, 1995, [Contains possibly excepted information: social security number on a release statement] (Box 2002/151-324)
    - Valdez, Joe vs. MHMR, 1995 (Box 2002/151-324)
    - Velasco, Suzanne and Manny vs. MHMR, 1995 (Box 2002/151-324)
    - Ventle, Melanie vs. TDCJ, 1995 (Box 2002/151-324)
    - Villareal vs. DHS, 1995, [Contains possibly excepted information: common law privacy] (Box 2002/151-324)
    - Walker, Ellis D. and Charolette A. vs. State of Texas, 1995 (Box 2002/151-324)
    - Walker, Fredrick and Evelyn V. vs. TDCJ, 1995 (Box 2002/151-324)
    - Wells, Linda and Jerry vs. MHMR, 1995 (Box 2002/151-324)
    - Williams, Esther and Walter A. and State Farm Mutual Automobile Insurance Co. vs. TYC, 1995 (Box 2002/151-324)
    - Wilson, Barbara and Harry vs. TPWD, 1995 (Box 2002/151-324)
    - Wilson, Marshal and Pamela and United Service Automobile Association vs. TDCJ, 1995 (Box 2002/151-324)
    - Wilson, Marsel and Pamela vs. TDCJ, 1995 (Box 2002/151-324)
    - Young, Jay and Kathy vs. DPS, 1995 (Box 2002/151-324)
    - Zavala, Jose vs. TDCJ, 1995 (Box 2002/151-324)
    - Zuberbueler, Robert vs. DPS, 1995 (Box 2002/151-324)
    - List of lawsuit settlements (Box 2002/151-324)
  - Group two settlement files, January 1995-July 1996
    - Box 1 inventory (Box 2002/151-324)
    - Ackerman, Misti vs. DPS, 1995 (Box 2002/151-324)
    - Adams, Linda C. vs. State of Texas, 1995 (Box 2002/151-324)
    - Alamo Rental Car Co. vs. Texas Dept. of Agriculture, 1995 (Box 2002/151-324)
    - Alberti, Lawrence, et al, vs. Sheriff, Harris County vs. George Bush, 1996 (Box 2002/151-324)
    - Alcala, Raul vs. TEC, 1996 (Box 2002/151-324)
    - Anchondo, Frances vs. MHMR, 1995-1996 (Box 2002/151-324)
    - Appiah, Rose vs. DPS, 1996 (Box 2002/151-324)
    - Archuleta vs. TDCJ, 1996, [Contains possibly excepted information: common law privacy] (Box 2002/151-324)
    - Arnold, Jeridean, Ernest Land and Verenda Smith vs. TDCJ, 1996 (Box 2002/151-324)
    - Asabere, Ebenezer vs. MHMR, 1996 (Box 2002/151-324)
    - Ashworth, Suzette vs. TDPRS, 1995-1996 (Box 2002/151-324)
    - AVIS Rent A Car vs. MHMR, 1995 (Box 2002/151-324)
    - Baca, Rodolfo vs. Richard Ladd, Texas Dept. of Health, 1994-1996, [Contains possibly excepted information: common law privacy] (Box 2002/151-324)
    - Barber, Beverly vs. MHMR, 1995 (Box 2002/151-324)
    - Baylor, Raymond V. vs. TDCJ, 1996 (Box 2002/151-324)
    - Beil, Jack B. vs. TDCJ, 1996 (Box 2002/151-324)
    - Belk, Joe and Tammy vs. GLO, 1996 (Box 2002/151-324)
    - Berk, George and USAA Casualty Insurance Co. vs. DPS, 1996 (Box 2002/151-324)
    - Beltram, Christopher vs. MHMR, 1996 (Box 2002/151-324)
    - Bill's Pharmacy vs. Texas Dept. of Health and DHS, 1995 (Box 2002/151-324)
    - Blakemore, Elvire Sanders vs. MHMR, 1996 (Box 2002/151-324)
    - Bohanon, Robert vs. TDCJ, 1996 (Box 2002/151-324)
    - Borders, Michael vs. DPS, 1996 (Box 2002/151-324)
    - Borjas, Sylvia vs. DPS, 1996 (Box 2002/151-324)
    - Boyken, Tony E. vs. TDCJ, 1996 (Box 2002/151-324)
    - Brannon, Lavelle vs. MHMR, 1996 (Box 2002/151-324)
    - Briggs, Kenneth vs. Comptroller, 1995-1996, [Contains possibly excepted information: common law privacy] (Box 2002/151-324)
    - Brown, Matthew Robert vs. DPS, 1996 (Box 2002/151-324)
    - Burnett Dairy Queen vs. MHMR, 1995-1996 (Box 2002/151-325)
    - Butoryak, Zachary vs. MHMR, 1996 (Box 2002/151-325)
    - Cade, Mary Jo vs. MHMR, 1995-1996 (Box 2002/151-325)
    - Calvert, Susan vs. TYC, 1996 (Box 2002/151-325)
    - Campbell's Portable Buildings vs. DPS, 1996 (Box 2002/151-325)
    - Cardoza vs. Texas Employment Commission (TEC), 1995-1996, [Contains possibly excepted information: common law privacy] (Box 2002/151-325)
    - Carr, Richard vs. MHMR, 1995-1996 (Box 2002/151-325)
    - Carrasco, Juan vs. Texas Transportation Institute, et al, 1995-1996 (Box 2002/151-325)
    - Carraway, Freddie vs. TDCJ, 1995-1996 (Box 2002/151-325)
    - Carreras, Robert vs. MHMR, 1996 (Box 2002/151-325)
    - Cervin, Marcella vs. MHMR, 1996 (Box 2002/151-325)
    - Champlain, Wallace, J., D.O. - indemnification, 1995 (Box 2002/151-325)
    - Chan, Linda vs. MHMR, 1995-1996 (Box 2002/151-325)
    - Charba, Mary Ann vs. Texas Dept. of Agriculture, 1996 (Box 2002/151-325)
    - Chiminello, Phillip vs. DHS, 1996, [Contains possibly excepted information: common law privacy, home address of state employee] (Box 2002/151-325)
    - Christian, Levi vs. TPWD, 1996 (Box 2002/151-325)
    - City of Rosenberg and Frederick V. Hackett vs. MHMR, 1996 (Box 2002/151-325)
    - Clark, Jean, et al. vs. UT Health Science Center, 1996 (Box 2002/151-325)
    - Clarkson, Speagin vs. MHMR, 1995-1996 (Box 2002/151-325)
    - Clift, Roderick vs. Ping Ching Kwang and GSC, 1995-1996, [Contains possibly excepted information: driver's license number, vehicle id number, license plate number, home address of state employee] (Box 2002/151-325)
    - Collier, Rebecca G. vs. TDPRS, 1995-1996, [Contains possibly excepted information: common law privacy] (Box 2002/151-325)
    - Cook, Kirsten, et al. vs. UT Medical Branch, 1996 (Box 2002/151-325)
    - Cordell, Richard Charles vs. Robert E. Mastin, 1996 (Box 2002/151-325)
    - Cortez, H. vs. MHMR, 1996 (Box 2002/151-325)
    - Cotham, W. Mark vs. Antonio Garza, 1995-1996 (Box 2002/151-325)
    - Craft, Stanley Leon Don and Becky L. vs. TDCJ, 1996 (Box 2002/151-325)
    - Crowson vs. TDCJ, 1996, [Contains possibly excepted information: attorney work product, social security numbers] (Box 2002/151-325)
    - Culpepper, Sandy vs. Texas School for the Deaf, 1996 (Box 2002/151-325)
    - Cunniff, Celamaine (TDPRS), 1994-1996 (Box 2002/151-325)
    - Davidson, Dana vs. TDCJ, 1996 (Box 2002/151-325)
    - Davis, Lawrence vs. MHMR, 1995-1996 (Box 2002/151-325)
    - Davis, Mary Ann vs. Texas Dept. of Health, 1995-1996, [Contains possibly excepted information: common law privacy] (Box 2002/151-325)
    - Deleon, Juan vs. Allen Steen (TYC), 1995-1996 (Box 2002/151-325)
    - Delicate, Cedilla vs. MHMR, 1995 (Box 2002/151-325)
    - De Los Santos, Gilberto vs. UT Pan American, 1996 (Box 2002/151-325)
    - Dempsey vs. GLO and Veterans Land Board, 1995 (Box 2002/151-325)
    - Denton, Mary E. vs. TPWD, 1996, [Contains possibly excepted information: common law privacy, home address of state employee] (Box 2002/151-325)
    - Dickson, Katherine and Continental Insurance Co. vs. MHMR, 1996 (Box 2002/151-325)
    - Dobroski, Mark vs. MHMR, 1996 (Box 2002/151-325)
    - Dodd, Jonathan vs. MHMR, 1995-1996 (Box 2002/151-325)
    - Doe, Michelle vs. U.S., et al, 1995-1996 (Box 2002/151-325)
    - Doneghy, Bobbie vs. TDCJ, 1996 (Box 2002/151-325)
    - Dorn, Darryl M. vs. Attorney General, 1996, [Contains possibly excepted information: common law privacy] (Box 2002/151-325)
    - Douglass, Jan and Patricia vs. DPS, 1995 (Box 2002/151-325)
    - Drinkard, Melba vs. TxDOT, 1995-1996 (Box 2002/151-325)
    - Dudley vs. MHMR, 1995 (Box 2002/151-325)
    - Espinoza, Ruth vs. TxDOT, 1996, [Contains possibly excepted information: common law privacy] (Box 2002/151-325)
    - Essex, Stephanie and Brian vs. MHMR, 1995-1996 (Box 2002/151-325)
    - Evans, Alan T. vs. TDCJ, 1995-1996 (Box 2002/151-325)
    - Evans, B. vs. TDCJ, 1995-1996 (Box 2002/151-325)
    - Evans, Ida vs. MHMR, 1995-1996 (Box 2002/151-325)
    - Finley, Roy G. vs. TPWD, 1995 (Box 2002/151-325)
    - Fitts, Jerry vs. TPWD, 1996 (Box 2002/151-325)
    - Fleitman Drink Sales vs. TYC, 1996 (Box 2002/151-325)
    - Flores, Ernesto X. vs. MHMR, 1996 (Box 2002/151-325)
    - Flores, Gloria B. vs. TYC, 1995-1996 (Box 2002/151-325)
    - Flores, Maria vs. MHMR, 1995-1996 (Box 2002/151-325)
    - Flores, Rosemary vs. Texas Department of Insurance, et al, 1996, [Contains possibly excepted information: common law privacy] (Box 2002/151-325)
    - Flores, Roxanne and Jose vs. Railroad Commission, 1996 (Box 2002/151-325)
    - Fort, Kevin vs. TABC, 1995-1996 (Box 2002/151-325)
    - Foster, Lloyd D. vs. DPS, 1996 (Box 2002/151-325)
    - Francis, Debra Jo vs. MHMR, 1995 (Box 2002/151-325)
    - Fuchs, Stella G. vs. TDCJ, 1996 (Box 2002/151-325)
    - Galle, Laurie vs. MHMR, 1995-1996 (Box 2002/151-325)
    - Galvez, Irma L. vs. Ken Kennamer, 1996 (Box 2002/151-325)
    - Garcia, Rita and David, State Farm Mutual Automobile Insurance Co. vs. DPS, 1996 (Box 2002/151-325)
    - Garcia, Sandra vs. TDCJ and Elvin Young, 1995 (Box 2002/151-325)
    - Garza, Justina vs. TYC, 1996 (Box 2002/151-325)
    - Gasperon, Sonnie and Wade vs. MHMR, 1996 (Box 2002/151-325)
    - Gates, Leighton vs. MHMR, 1996 (Box 2002/151-325)
    - Gerry, Kimberly vs. Bill C. Lipsey, 1996 (Box 2002/151-325)
    - Gilbert, et al. vs. MHMR, 1996, [Contains possibly excepted information: common law privacy] (Box 2002/151-325)
    - Girard, Dana vs. University of Houston, 1996 (Box 2002/151-325)
    - Golden, Linda vs. TDCJ, 1996, [Contains possibly excepted information: common law privacy] (Box 2002/151-325)
    - Gonzales, Raul vs. Attorney General's Office, 1996, [Contains possibly excepted information: common law privacy] (Box 2002/151-325)
    - Gonzales, Raymond R. vs. UT Medical Branch, 1995-1996 (Box 2002/151-325)
    - Gonzales, Rosa vs. MHMR, 1996 (Box 2002/151-325)
    - Gonzales, et al. vs. Kaster, et al, 1995-1996, [Contains possibly excepted information: social security number] (Box 2002/151-325)
    - Green, C.O. vs. O'Brien, Harold, 1996 (Box 2002/151-325)
    - Grifzu, Robert L. vs. TDCJ, 1995-1996 (Box 2002/151-325)
    - Guadjuardo, Darlene vs. TPWD, 1996 (Box 2002/151-325)
    - Box inventory (Box 2002/151-325)
    - Guerrero, Michael and Kristi vs. Wayne Francis and TDCJ, 1996 (Box 2002/151-325)
    - Guerrero, Tammy et al. vs. MHMR, 1995-1996 (Box 2002/151-325)
    - Guzman, Clifford vs. A. Maxwell and TDCJ, 1996 (Box 2002/151-325)
    - Guzman, Robert D. vs. MHMR, 1995-1996 (Box 2002/151-325)
    - Hall, Stafford O. vs. TDCJ, 1995-1996 (Box 2002/151-325)
    - Hansen vs, Texas Natural Resource Conservation Commission (TNRCC), 1995 (Box 2002/151-325)
    - Harper, David vs. MHMR, 1995-1996 (Box 2002/151-325)
    - Harris, Laura vs. Vida Y Salud-Health Care Systems, 1996 (Box 2002/151-325)
    - Harvey, Sammy vs. MHMR, 1995-1996 (Box 2002/151-325)
    - Hawkins Service Station vs. TDCJ, 1996 (Box 2002/151-325)
    - Haynes, Myra vs. UT Medical Branch, 1996, [Contains possibly excepted information: common law privacy] (Box 2002/151-325)
    - Hays, Bernice E. and Kenneth F. vs. TPWD, 1995 (Box 2002/151-325)
    - Hernandez vs. TNRCC, 1996 (Box 2002/151-325)
    - Hernandez, Luciano vs. TABC, 1995 (Box 2002/151-325)
    - Hernandez, Mariano P. vs. State of Texas, 1996, [Contains possibly excepted information: common law privacy] (Box 2002/151-325)
    - Hernandez, Mary Jane vs. MHMR, 1996 (Box 2002/151-325)
    - Hernandez, Yolanda and Jose vs. TDCJ, 1996 (Box 2002/151-325)
    - Hewlett, Don, Chevrolet-Oldsmobile... vs. Texas School for the Deaf, 1996 (Box 2002/151-326)
    - Hidalgo, Bertha vs. TDCJ, 1995 (Box 2002/151-326)
    - Hicks, Perry L. vs. Wesley Warner, TDCJ, et al, 1996 (Box 2002/151-326)
    - Hill, John vs. Robert James Bullock and DPS, 1995-1996, [Contains possibly excepted information: common law privacy] (Box 2002/151-326)
    - Hill, Linda and Allstate Insurance vs. MHMR, Denton State School, 1996 (Box 2002/151-326)
    - Hill, Shyrel vs. TDCJ, 1996 (Box 2002/151-326)
    - Hinds vs. DHS, 1992-1996 (Box 2002/151-326)
    - Hitchcock, K.E. and ITT Hartford vs. TDCJ, 1996 (Box 2002/151-326)
    - Hixson, Christopher vs. DPS, 1996 (Box 2002/151-326)